FADHIL DHAFIR MOHAMMED

Hay Al-Qadisiyah, Baghdad, Iraq. | (H) +964 (0) 771 182 8872 | fadhil.dhafir96@gmail.com

Professional Summary

A Multitasking project manager/coordinator with experience in planning projects and preparing financial and progress reports. In addition to managing resources and information, and assisting with scheduling, planning, and organizing meetings and project activities. A Motivated leader with strong organizational and prioritization abilities, and excellent communication and time-management skills, in addition to handling difficult tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

Skills

- Fluent in Arabic, and English.
- Experienced in problem-solving.
- Enthusiastic and committed.
- Work effectively both as team member and independently.
- Professional in using Microsoft Office programs.
- Effective use of multimedia in terms of marketing, advertising, and promoting.
- Professional in using Express Accounts-Accounting Software, and Peachtree Quantum 2010 Accountants' Edition.

Work Experience

Project Coordinator HAMA Group – Sulaimani, Iraq.

08/2018 to 03/2019

- Maintained and monitored project plans, project schedules, and working hours.
- Organized, planned, and participated in meetings.
- Documented and followed up on important actions and decisions from meetings.
- Provided administrative support as needed.
- Assessed project risks and issues and provided solutions where applicable.
- Created a project management calendar for fulfilling each goal and objective.

First Assistant Director HAMA Group – Sulaimani, Iraq.

08/2018 to 03/2019

- Used to be in charge of all pre-production, during production, and post-production activities.
- Assisted the director, coordinated all production activities, and supervised the cast and crew.
- Provided key link between the director, cast and crew.
- Liaised with/between the production office, and communication office.
- Provided daily regular progress reports about the shoot.

- Developed, implemented, and managed social media strategies.
- Managed and oversaw social media content.
- Worked with designers to ensure content is informative and appealing.
- Provided constructive feedback.

Stock Market Analyst Rabee Securities – Sulaimani, Iraq.

01/2018 to 07/2018

- Analyzed annual financial reports of banks, and companies in the ISX (Iraq Stock Exchange).
- Analyzed and translated auditor's notes and calculations.
- Translated, evaluated, and calculated data to customers (Investors).
- Established trading accounts in the ISX (Irag Stock Exchange).

Student Support Assistant AUIS – Sulaimani, Iraq.

12/2016 to 05/2017

- Assisted students in classroom activity (e.g.) working with written materials.
- Toke responsibility for the preparation, upkeep, and organization of resources.
- Attended and contributed to course team meetings, site meetings, tutorials, and curriculum development as part of the evaluation process.

Volunteer Staff (Member of PFO) Peace Festival Organization – Baghdad, Iraq.

07/2013 to 04/2016

- Prevented violence and hatred between individuals
- Worked with conflict as a creative force for change.
- Organized events, and seminars for spreading peace.

Education

The American University of Iraq – Sulaimani.

Sulaimani, Iraq. May 2019

- Bachelor of Science, Business Administration, B.B.A.
- · Majoring in BA.
- Minoring in Gender Studies.